<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="candidate_names">
        <item>Hillary Clinton</item>
        <item>Donald Trump</item>
        <item>Jill Stein</item>
        <item>Gary Johnson</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="candidate_parties">
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Libertarian</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="policy_categories">
        <item>Social Policy</item>
        <item>Economic Policy</item>
        <item>Foreign Policy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="social_policy_questions">
        <item>Same sex marriage should be legal.</item>
        <item>The Black Lives Matter movement has raised important issues
        that need to be addressed.</item>
        <item>Abortion destroys an innocent life and should be illegal in all cases.</item>
        <item>The large amounts of money involved in elections is nothing short of corruption.</item>
        <item>More gun control measures only prevents law abiding citizens from
        protecting themselves.</item>
        <item>Marijuana is dangerous and should be illegal.</item>
        <item>Obamacare is a failure and must be repealed.</item>
        <item>Climate change is real and must be dealt with decisively.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="economic_policy_questions">
        <item>The richest Americans do not pay their fair share of taxes.</item>
        <item>High corporate taxes hinders economic growth.</item>
        <item>Minimum wage is too low and must be raised to $15 per hour.</item>
        <item>Wall Street should be subjected to more regulation to prevent
        another recession.</item>
        <item>Government investment in higher education has caused the massive increases
        in the cost of college.</item>
        <item>Social Security must be protected and not be privatized.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="foreign_policy_question">
        <item>We should formally declare war on ISIL</item>
        <item>We need to do our part in taking in more refugees.</item>
        <item>The nuclear deal with Iran prevented a war with Iran.</item>
        <item>Israel is our ally and we must protect them.</item>
        <item>Granting amnesty to illegal aliens only encourages
        their illegal behavior.</item>
        <item>We need a stronger military to protect our interests.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="social_policy_examples">
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Same sex marriage should be legal and LGBT people need their other rights protected as well
            \nAgree: Same sex marriage should be legal
            \nDisagree: Create something with the same legal effects as marriage, but call it something else
            \nStrongly Disagree: Same sex marriage should not be legal in any way
        </item> <!--Same sex marriage -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: They have raised important issues and we must go further with our criminal justice system reforms.
            \nAgree: They have raised important issues that need to be addressed
            \nDisagree: No, All Lives Matter
            \nStrongly Disagree: Black Lives Matter is an inherently racist movement trying to protect criminals
        </item> <!--black lives matter -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Abortion destroys an innocent life and should be illegal in all cases
            \nAgree: There should be exceptions for rape, incest, and threats to the mother’s life
            \nDisagree: Abortion should be legal in most cases
            \nStrongly Disagree: Abortion should be legal in all cases
        </item> <!--abortion -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Yes, and we must move to publicly funding campaigns
            \nAgree: The large amounts of money involved in elections is nothing short of corruption
            \nDisagree: One should be able to spend their money however they see fit
            \nStrongly Disagree: Donation limits to campaigns limit free speech and should be removed
        </item> <!--money in politics -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Gun control measures are already too extreme and need to be relaxed
            \nAgree: More gun control measures only prevents law abiding citizens from protecting themselves
            \nDisagree: We need to prevent criminals and terrorists from being able to purchase guns
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need to decrease the number of guns in our country
        </item> <!--guns -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We need harsher penalties for drug use
            \nAgree: Marijuana is dangerous and should be illegal
            \nDisagree: Marijuana should be decriminalized
            \nStrongly Disagree: Marijuana (and other currently illegal drugs) should be legalized
        </item> <!-- illegal drugs -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Obamacare is not just a failure, but also unconstitutional
            \nAgree: Obamacare is a failure and must be repealed
            \nDisagree: Obamacare has been a good start to health care reform and we should build upon it
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need to go further than Obamacare and offer single-payer health care
        </item> <!-- health care -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Climate change is real and we are not moving fast enough to stop it
            \nAgree: Climate change is real and our current rate of action is good enough
            \nDisagree: Climate change is real, but we have other issues that are more important to address
            \nStrongly Disagree: Climate change is not real
        </item> <!-- climate change -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="economic_policy_examples">
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We need significantly higher taxes on the rich
            \nAgree: We need should slightly raise taxes on the rich
            \nDisagree: Taxes for the rich should be lowered to create jobs
            \nStrongly Disagree: Taxes for everyone should be lowered
        </item> <!-- income taxes -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Yes and we should instead tax consumption
            \nAgree: Yes and we should cut the corporate tax rate
            \nDisagree: The corporate tax rate is good where it is
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need higher taxes on corporations
        </item> <!-- corporate taxes -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: Yes, it should be raised $15 per hour
            \nAgree: Yes, it should be raised to $12 per hour
            \nDisagree: The current minimum wage is good where it is
            \nStrongly Disagree: The current minimum wage destroys jobs and needs to be reduced or abolished
        </item> <!-- minimum wage -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We need more regulation of not only Wall Street, but also banks
            \nAgree: We should strengthen and enforce our current regulations
            \nDisagree: We already have enough regulation of Wall Street
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need to roll back the regulation of Wall Street
        </item> <!-- wall street reform -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We also need to remove the excessive regulations imposed on schools
            \nAgree: The federal government should not be giving loans for college education
            \nDisagree: We should invest more in vocational schools
            \nStrongly Disagree: We should pay for everyone to get a college education
        </item> <!-- higher education -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We also need to expand Social Security benefits
            \nAgree: Social Security must be protected
            \nDisagree: We should allow people to instead invest their own money
            \nStrongly Disagree: Social Security is a Ponzi Scheme that needs to be abolished
        </item> <!-- social security -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="foreign_policy_examples">
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We are at war with radical Islam and we should treat it as such
            \nAgree: We should increase our presence in the Middle East through funding the groups currently fighting ISIL
            \nDisagree: We should focus more on preventing domestic terrorism
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need to pull back from the Middle East before we create even more instability
        </item> <!-- fighting isil -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We should be taking in even more refugees
            \nAgree: We are currently taking in enough refugees
            \nDisagree: We should not accept any more refugees from the Middle East
            \nStrongly Disagree: We should not accept any refugees
        </item> <!-- refugee crisis -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: The Iran nuclear deal was a very good agreement
            \nAgree: The Iran nuclear deal was not perfect, but it at least prevented another war in the Middle East
            \nDisagree: We gave up too much in the Iran nuclear deal
            \nStrongly Disagree: We should void the Iran nuclear deal
        </item> <!-- iran nuclear deal -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We should support our ally in all of their international conflicts
            \nAgree: We should support Israel and a two state solution to their conflict with Palestine
            \nDisagree: We should only support Israel through the UN
            \nStrongly Disagree: We should not support Israel due to their illegal treatment of Palestine
        </item> <!-- israel -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We need to deport all illegal aliens and prevent more from entering
            \nAgree: We can allow illegal aliens to stay as guest workers and commit to protecting the border
            \nDisagree: We should give amnesty to illegal aliens and a pathway to citizenship and commit to protecting the border
            \nStrongly Disagree: We should give amnesty to illegal aliens, a pathway to citizenship, and make it easier for more people to legally move to the US
        </item> <!-- immigration -->
        <item>
            Strongly Agree: We must be prepared for any threat that currently faces us as well as any future threats
            \nAgree: The current size of the military is good
            \nDisagree: We should focus more on taking care of our veterans
            \nStrongly Disagree: We need to reduce the size of the military
        </item> <!-- size of the military -->
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="clinton_social_answers">
        <item>2</item> <!--Same sex marriage -->
        <item>1</item> <!--black lives matter -->
        <item>-1</item> <!--abortion -->
        <item>1</item> <!--money in politics -->
        <item>-2</item> <!--guns -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- illegal drugs -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- health care -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- climate change -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="clinton_economic_answers">
        <item>1</item> <!-- income taxes -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- corporate taxes -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- minimum wage -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- wall street reform -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- higher education -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- social security -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="clinton_foreign_answers">
        <item>1</item> <!-- fighting isil -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- refugee crisis -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- iran nuclear deal -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- israel -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- immigration -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- size of the military -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="trump_social_answers">
        <item>0</item> <!--Same sex marriage -->
        <item>-2</item> <!--black lives matter -->
        <item>1</item> <!--abortion -->
        <item>1</item> <!--money in politics -->
        <item>2</item> <!--guns -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- illegal drugs -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- health care -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- climate change -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="trump_economic_answers">
        <item>-1</item> <!-- income taxes -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- corporate taxes -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- minimum wage -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- wall street reform -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- higher education -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- social security -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="trump_foreign_answers">
        <item>2</item> <!-- fighting isil -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- refugee crisis -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- iran nuclear deal -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- israel -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- immigration -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- size of the military -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="stein_social_answers">
        <item>2</item> <!--Same sex marriage -->
        <item>2</item> <!--black lives matter -->
        <item>-2</item> <!--abortion -->
        <item>2</item> <!--money in politics -->
        <item>-2</item> <!--guns -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- illegal drugs -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- health care -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- climate change -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="stein_economic_answers">
        <item>2</item> <!-- income taxes -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- corporate taxes -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- minimum wage -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- wall street reform -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- higher education -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- social security -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="stein_foreign_answers">
        <item>-2</item> <!-- fighting isil -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- refugee crisis -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- iran nuclear deal -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- israel -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- immigration -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- size of the military -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="johnson_social_answers">
        <item>1</item> <!--Same sex marriage -->
        <item>0</item> <!--black lives matter -->
        <item>-1</item> <!--abortion -->
        <item>-2</item> <!--money in politics -->
        <item>2</item> <!--guns -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- illegal drugs -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- health care -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- climate change -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="johnson_economic_answers">
        <item>-1</item> <!-- income taxes -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- corporate taxes -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- minimum wage -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- wall street reform -->
        <item>2</item> <!-- higher education -->
        <item>-2</item> <!-- social security -->
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="johnson_foreign_answers">
        <item>-1</item> <!-- fighting isil -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- refugee crisis -->
        <item>1</item> <!-- iran nuclear deal -->
        <item>0</item> <!-- israel -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- immigration -->
        <item>-1</item> <!-- size of the military -->
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="clinton_issues">
        <item>Addition and substance use</item>
        <item>Treating autism</item>
        <item>Campaign finance reform</item>
        <item>Ending campus sexual assault</item>
        <item>Fighting climate change</item>
        <item>Criminal justice reform</item>
        <item>Disability rights</item>
        <item>Early childhood education</item>
        <item>Fixing America\'s infrastructure</item>
        <item>Gun violence prevention</item>
        <item>Affordable health care</item>
        <item>Fighting HIV and AIDS</item>
        <item>Immigration reform</item>
        <item>K-12 Education</item>
        <item>Labor and workers\' rights</item>
        <item>LGBT rights and equality</item>
        <item>Making college affordable</item>
        <item>Manufacturing jobs</item>
        <item>National security</item>
        <item>Paid family leave</item>
        <item>Protecting animals and wildlife</item>
        <item>Racial justice</item>
        <item>Raising incomes and fighting inequality</item>
        <item>Rural communities</item>
        <item>Seeking a cure for Alzheimer\'s disease</item>
        <item>Small business</item>
        <item>Social Security and Medicare</item>
        <item>Supporting veterans</item>
        <item>Expanding voting rights</item>
        <item>Wall Street reform</item>
        <item>Women\'s rights</item>
        <item>Workforce skills and job training</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="trump_issues">
        <item>Pay for the wall</item>
        <item>Health care reform</item>
        <item>U.S.-China trade reform</item>
        <item>Veterans administration reform</item>
        <item>Tax reform</item>
        <item>Second amendment rights</item>
        <item>Immigration reform</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stein_issues">
        <item>Climate action</item>
        <item>Jobs as a right</item>
        <item>Support for labor</item>
        <item>End poverty</item>
        <item>Health care as a right</item>
        <item>Education as a right</item>
        <item>A just economy</item>
        <item>Freedom and Equality</item>
        <item>Criminal justice reform</item>
        <item>Justice for all</item>
        <item>Peace and Human Rights</item>
        <item>Empower the people</item>
        <item>A Humane federal budget with fair taxes</item>
        <item>Financial reform</item>
        <item>Housing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="johnson_issues">
        <item>Ending wasteful spending</item>
        <item>Fixing our tax code, and cutting taxes</item>
        <item>Term limits</item>
        <item>Creating jobs for all Americans</item>
        <item>Personal freedom</item>
        <item>Foreign Policy and National Defense</item>
        <item>Immigration</item>
        <item>Criminal Justice Reform</item>
        <item>Internet freedom and security</item>
        <item>Environment</item>
        <item>Education</item>
        <item>Abortion</item>
        <item>The War on Drugs</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>